www.tvsubtitles.net
Do you really think I'll let you
sell her like a common whore?
Dorne is the safest
place for her.
- You cannot stop it.
- No!
No, wait.
It wasn't her.
You can't avenge him if you're dead.
On behalf of the warlocks
of Qarth, I welcome you.
It would be an honor to host you
at the House of the Undying,
Mother of Dragons.
Stannis will be here
in an hour.
Renly's bannermen
will flock to him.
Calling yourself king
doesn't make you one.
And if Renly wasn't a king,
I wasn't a queen.
- Do you want to be a queen?
- I want to be the queen.
There on that mountain.
We need to get rid
of those lookouts.
I need to move fast
and silent.
Lord Commander,
I'd like to join Lord Qhorin.
Aye.
Are you going
to kill Joffrey?
- If the Gods give me strength.
- And then what?
First we have to
win the war.
You never told me
where you're from.
Volantis.
You're one of them now.
I should have let you burn.
You saved me
and the two I was with.
You stole three deaths
from the Red God.
- Speak three names.
- I can name anyone?
- And you'll kill him?
- A man has said.
The one who tortures everyone.
They call him the Tickler.
The Stony Shore's not far
from Torrhen's Square.
More impressive prize than
a few fisherman's daughters.
Soon as Winterfell got word that
we'd taken Torrhen's Square,
the Starks would send
their men to take it back.
Take me to my ship.
Lord Stark, Torrhen's Square
is under siege.
Torrhen's Square is barely
40 leagues from here.
Go, Ser Rodrik.
Take the men you need.
What did you see
in your dream?
That the sea came
to Winterfell.
Drowned men were
floating in the yard.
Ser Rodrik
was one of them.
( Theme music playing )
??Game of Thrones 2x06 ??/font>
The Old Gods and the New
Original Air Date on May 6, 2012
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
??
Subtitles downloaded from www.OpenSubtitles.org
I've taken your castle.
- Theon?
- It's Prince Theon now.
Get up.
You have to get dressed.
I've taken Winterfell.
I took it.
I'm occupying it.
I sent men over the walls
with grappling claws and ropes.
- Why?
- To take the castle.
- You went with Robb.
- And he sent me back to Pyke.
I'm a Greyjoy. I can't fight
for Robb and my father both.
- Where's Hodor?
- I don't know.
Find the Halfwit.
My men are bringing your people
together in the courtyard.
Why?
So you and I can
go down and tell them
- how you've yielded Winterfell to me.
- I won't.
Yes, you will.
I won't.
I'll never yield.
We'll fight you
and throw you out.
The castle is mine,
but these people
are still yours.
You'll yield
to keep them safe,
to keep them alive.
That's what a good
lord would do.
Think carefully about
what you want to say.
Theon.
Did you hate us
the whole time?
I've yielded
Winterfell to Theon.
Louder.
Say Prince Theon.
I've yielded Winterfell
to Prince Theon.
You all know me.
Aye, we know you for
a steaming sack of shit.
Farlen, you be silent.
Listen to your
little Lord, Farlen.
He has more sense
than you do.
All of you should do
as he commands.
My father has donned the
ancient crown of salt and rock
and declared himself
King of the Iron Islands.
He claims the North as well
by right of conquest.
You are all his subjects.
Bugger that.
I serve the Starks.
If you think you can
hold the North with this--
Shut up!
If you serve me as loyally
as you served Ned Stark,
I will be as good to you
as he ever was.
Betray me, and you will
wish you hadn't.
Maester Luwin,
send a raven to Pyke
informing my father
of my victory here
and one to Deepwood Motte
to my sister.
Inform her that she's
to bring 500 men to Winterfell.
You are a Maester
of the Citadel
sworn to serve the lord
of Winterfell, are you not?
I am.
I am the Lord
of Winterfell
as Bran just informed you.
Send the ravens.
My Lord.
My Lord Greyjoy.
I see you've finally learned
how to address your betters.
What do you want?
I was brought here
a captive.
You were here the day
I was taken.
I'm the one who took you.
What of it?
Let me serve you.
Serve me how?
I need fighters,
not kitchen sluts.
It was Robb Stark who
put me in the kitchens.
Put a spear
in my hand again.
So you can bury it
in my neck?
Do you take me
for a fool?
Get up.
Step aside.
Why?
It's your dream,
Little Lord.
The ocean has come
to swallow this place.
I ain't letting it
drown me.
- And in a few days' time--
Greyjoy!
What have they
done to him?
We caught this one on this way
back from Torrhen's Square.
Took out two of ours
before I got his sword.
Ser Rodrik, it grieves me that
we meet as foes.
It grieves me you've less honor
than a back alley whore.
You were raised here
under this roof.
- These people are your people.
- They are not my people.
King Robb thought of you
as a brother.
My brothers are dead.
They died fighting
Stark men, men like you.
Aye, they died fighting
a war your father started.
Lord Stark raised you
among his own sons.
Among them,
but not one of them.
I was his hostage
taken from my home.
If he were alive
to see this--
He's not.
He's dead.
The Seven Kingdoms
are at war.
And Winterfell is mine.
I should have put
a sword in your belly
instead of
in your hand.
You've served this House
faithfully, old man.
But keep talking
and I'll--
Take him to the cells.
Lock him up--
My prince,
you cannot let that stand.
He must pay.
I'll lock him in a cell
until he rots--
No, he has to pay
the iron price.
They'll never respect
you while he lives.
Ser Rodrik,
I sentence you to death.
No! You said no harm
would come to them if I yielded.
The old man couldn't
keep his mouth shut.
I urge you not to make
a hasty decision.
He disrespected me
in front of my men.
That was his decision,
not mine.
He is worth more
to you alive than dead.
The Starks will pay.
Please, Theon,
think what you do.
You'll address me
as Prince Theon
or you'll be next.
Come.
No!
- No!
- Theon!
Please!
Ser Rodrik!
He who passes the sentence
should swing the sword.
- I'm begging you!
- Coward.
Stop! Stop right now!
You don't give commands anymore,
Little Lord.
- Please, stop this. Please stop him.
- Hush now, child.
I'm off to see your father.
You said no harm
would come!
You said no harm would come.
Theon, please.
Any last words, old man?
Gods help you,
Theon Greyjoy.
Now you are truly lost.
Theon, please, don't.
- Do something.
- I'll do anything. Please!
No, please, stop it!
Ghost, stay with us.
Ghost!
There goes your pet.
He's not a pet.
You're right,
he's not.
You can't tame
a wild thing.
You can't trust
- Ghost is different.
- So you think.
Wild creatures
have their own rules,
their own reasons.
And you'll never
know them.
Now the wildlings
we're looking for
sleep during the day
and hunt at night.
I thought you said
you couldn't know wild things.
I said you can't.
They find a nice cave
to hide in while the sun's up
and do their killing
when it's dark.
- We could do the same.
- No, we couldn't.
This is their country.
They know where to walk,
where not to walk.
I've lost good men
who fell into a crevasse
they didn't see
till they were in it.
My father always said
I'm of the North.
- I wasn't joking.
- Look around, boy.
This look like
home to you?
You start thinking
you know this place, it'll kill you.
You understand me?
No, you don't.
We're at war.
We've always been at war.
It's never going to end 'cause
we're not fighting an enemy.
We're fighting the North
and it's not going anywhere.
The Watch has given
you a great gift.
You only have one thing
to give in return--
your life.
I'll gladly give my life.
I don't want you
to be glad about it.
I want you to curse
and fight
until your heart's
done pumping.
And know this, boy--
your death will be a gift
for them south of the Wall.
They'll never know
what you've done.
how you died.
They won't even
know your damn name,
but they'll be alive because
some nameless bastard
north of the Wall
gave his life for theirs.
Now, do you understand me?
I do.
You're even dumber
than you look.
It's just words, boy,
to keep us a little
warmer in the night,
make us feel like
we've got a purpose.
Come on.
We've got to find these
goat fuckers before night falls
and they find us.
- Can you read?
- My Lord?
Can you read?
This letter detailing
our infantry movements
was meant for Lord Damon
of House Marbrand.
It was sent to Lord Marlyn
of House Dormand.
My apologies, My Lord.
I must have--
Girl, fetch me the "History of the
Greater and the Lesser Houses."
It's the one on the--
My cupbearer can read
better than you.
To whom does House Dormand
owe allegiance?
My Lord, I--
To the Starks
of Winterfell!
Who have 20,000 men
and my son!
I judged you might be
good for something more
than brutalizing peasants.
I see I overestimated you.
If you ever put my son's
life at risk again, I'll...
Leave us.
Put the book away, girl.
Maybe you should devise our next
battle plan while you're about it.
- Lord Petyr Baelish.
- Hmmm.
Give us the room.
Clear all this.
- Lord Tywin.
- Baelish.
- Wine?
- Thank you.
What news
from the capital?
I travelled here directly
from Renly Baratheon's camp.
Ah, the late king Renly.
Rather a short reign.
Murdered by a woman,
I hear.
So they say.
There has been talk
of other forces at work,
dark forces.
Here.
Men love to blame demons
when their grand plans
unravel.
It is my belief
that a moment of chaos
affords opportunities
lost soon after.
You say that as if you were
the first man alive to think it.
Yes, a crisis
is an opportunity.
What other brilliant insights
have you brought me today?
After the Lannisters
and the Starks,
the Tyrells command
the largest host.
Their lands are the most
fertile in the Seven Kingdoms,
- feeding horses and soldiers.
- Yes, yes, yes.
The Tyrells have not yet declared
for any of the surviving kings.
Loras wants revenge. He blames
Stannis for Renly's death.
And Margaery--
Wants to be queen.
Yes, she does.
House Tyrell rebelled
against the Iron Throne,
- against my grandson.
- They did.
And perhaps that treason
should be punished
one day,
after Stannis and Robb Stark
are defeated.
More wine for Lord Baelish.
If you will allow me to represent
your family's interests,
I believe that an advantageous
agreement--
The Tyrell host has
returned to Highgarden?
They have.
Pardon, My Lord.
It's only wine.
You would ride
there yourself?
Tonight, with your leave.
I'll have an answer
by nightfall.
That'll be all, girl.
What else?
On your son
Tyrion's directive,
I met with Catelyn Stark.
Why?
He had an interesting
proposal for her
- concerning her daughters.
- Hmm.
- A girl.
- A wildling.
We could question her.
You could.
She won't answer.
I've known a wildling to bite off
his tongue instead of talking.
- What's your name?
- Ygritte.
She was reaching for this axe
when you got to her.
Give her half a chance,
she'll bury it in your face.
I gave you my name.
I'm Jon Snow.
You ought to burn
them you killed.
We'd need a big
fire for that.
Tell me, Ygritte,
why do you want us
to build a big fire?
Are there some more
friends in the area?
Burn them or maybe you'll
need those swords again.
Our boy here's already
killed one dead man.
He can do it again
if he has to.
What waits
beyond the pass?
- The Free Folk.
- How many?
Hundreds and thousands.
More than you've
ever seen, Crow.
Why come to the mountains?
What's in the frostfangs
your king could want?
Do you mean to march
on the Wall?
Do you know
who I am, girl?
Qhorin Halfhand.
Tell me true.
If your people captured me,
would they take me prisoner?
They'd take your head
off your shoulders
if they was feeling kind.
If not,
they'd kill you slow.
We have no food for her.
Can't spare a man
to watch her.
Can't let her go. She'll bring
Mance Rayder's army down on us.
It needs to be done.
- Want me to do it?
- No.
No, I'll do it.
Come, brothers.
We'll leave him to it.
We'll meet you
at the top.
Don't take too long.
We're deep in
their country now.
You never killed
a woman before, did you?
You don't need
to do it.
Mance would take you.
I know he would.
There's secret ways.
The Crows would
never catch us.
I'm as much a Crow
as they are.
Will you burn me...
after?
Can't.
Someone might
see the smoke.
Strike hard and true,
Jon Snow,
or I'll come back
and haunt you.
That's cold.
Go on.
Be quick about it.
Do it.
Bastard, do it!
You can't do it.
We both know it.
The sun's going
down, Jon Snow.
And your friends
are nowhere close.
I'll find them.
Call for the
go on.
Call loudly.
May the Seven guide
the princess on her journey.
May the mother
give her health.
May the crone
give her wisdom.
May the warrior
give her courage.
One day I pray
you love someone.
I pray you love
her so much,
when you close your eyes,
you see her face.
I want that for you.
I want you to know what
it's like to love someone,
to truly love someone,
before I take her
from you.
You sound like a little cat mewling
for his mother.
Princes don't cry.
- I saw you cry.
- Did you say something, My Lady?
My little brother cried
when I left Winterfell.
So?
It seems a normal thing.
Is your little brother
a prince?
No.
Not really relevant,
then, is it?
Come, dog.
Hail, Joffrey!
Hail to the king.
Seven blessings on you,
Your Grace.
Murderer! Bastard!
All hail the king.
He's no king.
He's a bastard!
Please, Your Grace,
we're hungry.
- Freak!
- Get the prince back to the keep now.
Yes, My Lord.
Come, quickly.
Please, Your Grace,
give us some food!
Bread, Your Grace,
please!
Who threw that?
I want the man
who threw that.
Find who did that
and bring him to me!
- Hold on!
- Hold them back!
Just kill them!
Kill them all!
- Move. Move!
- Pull back!
Tear him to pieces!
What are you doing?
I want these people executed!
And they want
the same for you.
Where's Sansa?
Through the door!
Come on!
Protect the king!
- Get back!
- Fall back!
- Move!
- To the gates!
- Come in! Come in!
- Keep him safe!
Motherfucker!
- Watch out. Hold them back.
- Come on.
Hey!
Traitors!
I'll have
all their heads.
Oh, you blind,
bloody fool.
You can't insult me.
We've had vicious kings
and we've had idiot kings,
but I don't know if
we've ever been cursed with
a vicious idiot for a king.
- You can't--
- I can, I am.
They attacked me!
They threw a cow pie at you,
so you decided to kill them all?
They're starving,
you fool.
All because of a war
you started.
You're talking to a king!
And now I've struck a king.
Did my hand fall
from my wrist?
Where is the Stark girl?
Let them have her.
If she dies, you'll never
get your Uncle Jaime back.
You owe him quite a bit,
you know.
Where are you going?
You ever been fucked, little girl?
Come here.
Take some men and go and find
the Stark girl.
I take my orders
from the king.
This way!
Please!
No, no.
You're all right now,
little bird.
You're all right.
- We'll get you. We'll get you.
- This way.
Are you hurt,
My Lady?
The little bird's
bleeding.
Someone take her back
to her cage,
see to that cut.
Well done, Clegane.
I didn't do it for you.
He shouldn't
make me wait.
The Spice King is the second
wealthiest man in Qarth.
He makes everyone wait.
Of course, you could have
avoided this embarrassment
if you married
the wealthiest man in Qarth.
I already have a husband.
Khal Drogo is gone,
Khaleesi.
You are far too young
to be a widow forever
and far too beautiful.
And you are far too smart
to think that I will
succumb to flattery.
I have travelled
very far in my life
and met many women,
but none that are
immune to flattery.
- The Mother of Dragons!
- Ah.
Here he comes.
Forgive me. I had terrible
dreams last night.
Terrible dreams.
I could not sleep
until the sun was shining
and the birds were singing.
Look what a beauty you are
now the Red Waste
has been washed off you.
I am sorry about
all that unpleasantness.
The silver hair
of a true Targaryen.
Xaro Xhoan Daxos,
she is far too lovely
for a glorified
dockworker like yourself.
Very true, and yet they say
that your grandfather,
who sold pepper
off the back of a wagon,
married a lady far lovelier
and higher born than himself.
Every lady alive
was lovelier
and higher born
than my grandfather.
Ahem.
Did my servants not offer you
something to eat, to drink?
I'll have them flogged
in the square.
Thank you, My Lord.
You are a gracious host,
but there is no servant alive
that can bring me what I want.
Oh, she has a talent
for drama, this one.
So, my little princess,
what is it you want?
My birthright--
the Seven Kingdoms
of Westeros.
I fear I'm no better than
a servant in this regard.
I cannot give you
what I do not have.
I'm not asking you
for the Kingdoms.
I'm asking you
for ships.
I need to cross
the Narrow Sea.
I need my ships as well.
I use them, you see,
to bring spices from
one port to another.
Whatever you grant me
now will be repaid
three times over when
I retake the Iron Throne.
Retake?
Did you once sit
on the Iron Throne?
My father sat there
before he was murdered.
But if you did not
sit on it yourself,
would it not be correct
to say take the Iron Throne?
I didn't come here
to argue grammar.
Of course not.
You came to take my ships.
So let me explain
my position,
little princess.
Unlike you, I do not
have exalted ancestors.
I make my living by trade.
And I judge every trade
on its merits.
You ask for ships.
You say I shall be
repaid triple.
I do not doubt your honesty
or your intentions.
But before you
repay your debts,
you must seize
the Seven Kingdoms.
- Do you have an army?
- Not yet.
You do not have an army.
Do you have powerful
allies in Westeros?
There are many there
that support my claim.
When were you
there last?
I left when
I was a baby.
So, in truth,
you have no allies.
The people will rise
to fight for their rightful
Queen when I return.
Ah.
Forgive me,
little princess,
but I cannot make an investment
based on wishes and dreams.
Now if you'll pardon me.
Do you know Illyrio Mopatis,
Magister of Pentos?
Yes, we've met.
A shrewd man.
For my wedding he gave me
three petrified dragon eggs.
He believed--
the world believed--
that the ages
had turned them to stone.
How many centuries has it been
since dragons roamed the skies?
But I dreamt that
if I carried those eggs
into a great fire,
they would hatch.
When I stepped into the fire,
my own people thought I was mad.
But when the fire
burned out,
I was unhurt,
the Mother of Dragons.
Do you understand?
I'm no ordinary woman.
My dreams come true.
I admire your passion.
But in business, I trust
in logic, not passion.
I'm sorry, little princess.
I am not
your little princess.
I am Daenerys Stormborn
of the blood of old Valyria
and I will take
what is mine.
With fire and blood,
I will take it.
Yes, My Lady,
but not with my ships.
Who taught you to read?
My father, My Lord.
Hmm.
I taught my son
Jaime to read.
The Maester came
to me one day,
told me he wasn't learning.
He couldn't make sense
of the letters.
He reversed them
in his head.
The Maester said he'd heard
tell of this affliction
and that we simply
must accept it.
Ha!
After that,
I sat Jaime down
for four hours every day
until he learned.
He hated me for it,
for a time.
For a long time,
but he learned.
Where is your father?
Is he alive?
Who was he?
A stonemason.
A stonemason
who could read?
- Hmm.
- He taught himself.
Quite a man.
What killed him?
Loyalty.
You're a sharp
little thing, aren't you?
Did...
Forgive me, My Lord.
I shouldn't ask questions.
No...
But you've already begun.
Did you know
your father, My Lord?
I did.
I grew up with him.
I watched him
grow old.
He loved us.
He was a good man,
but a weak man,
a weak man who nearly destroyed
our House and name.
I'm cold.
I'll fetch more wood
for the fire, My Lord.
Mmm.
Where are you going, girl?
The armory,
My Lord.
Why?
Lord Tywin sent me.
What might this be?
Lord Tywin gave it to me.
What for?
To take to the armory.
Why would he do that?
Let's go and ask him.
Move!
Get out of the way!
Amory Lorch.
A girl has named
a second name.
A man will do
what must be done.
Now!
A girl cannot tell a man when
exactly he must do a thing.
A man cannot make a thing
happen before its time.
But he's going to tell Tywin.
He's getting away.
It has to be now.
Guard!
- Your Grace.
My honor, Your Grace.
Your Grace.
- Your Grace.
- Quent.
Lady Talisa.
Your Grace.
I'm not sure I'm a lady.
Westerosi customs are still
a bit foreign to me.
It's hard to keep
all the rules straight.
But if I remember
my lessons,
a woman of noble birth
is always called a lady
unless she's a queen
or a princess.
I could find
someone who knows.
Why are you so sure
I'm of noble birth?
Because it's obvious.
What if I told you my father
sold lace on the long bridge
and my mother, my brother, and I lived
with him above our shop?
I'd call you a liar.
Not very noble to accuse
a lady of dishonesty.
I always thought
I was a brilliant liar.
Better at amputations,
I'm afraid.
Quite a pretty spot.
Will we be here long?
I couldn't really discuss
troop movements with you.
I'm not a spy.
Of course a spy
would deny being a spy.
You're right.
You've found me out.
I'm writing a letter
to the Lannisters.
"The young wolf
is on the move."
Perhaps you'd join me...
If you've got time,
of course, for, well...
Robb.
Mother.
Mother, this is
Lady Talisa.
She's been helping
with the wounded.
She's been very...
helpful.
Lady Talisa.
Lady Stark.
Lady Talisa...?
- Maegyr.
- Maegyr?
Forgive me,
I do not know this name.
An uncommon name here.
An old name in Volantis.
Excuse me, My Lady.
Your Grace.
I've missed you.
Yes, you look
positively forlorn.
You surprised me,
that's all.
I didn't think
I'd see you today.
I wish that you were free
to follow your heart.
I know.
You have inherited your
father's responsibilities.
I'm afraid they come
at a cost.
- I know.
- You are promised to another--
a debt that must be paid.
- I haven't forgotten.
- Your Grace.
My Lady.
News from Winterfell.
Your brothers desert you?
I can tell you
which way to go.
We'll stop here.
Too dark to go
any farther today.
Here? There's no
shelter here.
There's no shelter
anywhere.
There is if you know
where to look.
The cold
could kill us both.
- If you light a fire--
- No fire.
- But a fire is--
Have it your way.
We'll stay warmer
if we stay close.
Bet you freeze to death
before I do.
Bet your life.
Think they're out
looking for you?
- Yes.
- Think they'll find you?
Yes.
You're brave.
Stupid,
but brave.
We start again at first light.
Get some sleep.
Stop moving.
I'm just trying
to get comfortable.
Stop it!
- You're still moving.
- Was I?
I didn't notice
that time.
This cannot be true.
We've had ravens
from White Harbor,
Barrowton
and the Dreadfort.
I'm afraid it is true.
Why?
Why would Theon--
Because the Greyjoys
are treasonous whores.
- My brothers?
- We've heard nothing of them.
But Rodrik Cassel is dead.
I told you,
never trust a Greyjoy!
I must go North at once.
There's still a war
to win, Your Grace.
How can I call myself king
if I can't hold my own castle?
How can I ask men
to follow me if I can't--
You are a king.
And that means you don't have
to do everything yourself.
Let me go
and talk to Theon.
There will be no talk.
He will die for this.
Theon holds the castle
with a skeleton crew.
Let me send word to
my bastard at the Dreadfort.
He can raise a few hundred men and
retake Winterfell before the new moon.
We have the Lannisters
on the run.
If you march all the way back north
now, you'll lose what you gained.
My boy would be honored to
bring you Prince Theon's head.
Tell your son Bran and Rickon's
safety is paramount.
And Theon-- I want him
brought to me alive.
I want to look him
in the eye and ask him why.
And then I'll take
his head myself.
Why on earth would I trust the word
of a lying little savage like you?
I'm no liar.
All wildlings
are liars and savages
with no loyalty
to anything or anyone.
I done what I had
to do to stay alive.
I hate the Starks
as well as you do.
Let me serve you,
My Lord.
How? And don't tell me
to put a spear in your hand.
There are other ways
to serve, My Lord.
I'm a prince now,
and you'd do well--
There are other ways
to serve, my prince.
Like what?
We know things,
the Free people.
You know things?
Like what?
How to eat dirt?
Other things.
Savage things.
Wait outside.
I always wondered
what you had under there.
It comes at a price.
I'm not killing you.
That's your price.
I already had that.
What do you want, then,
other than
your miserable life?
What all free people want--
my freedom.
Well, you shall
have it, then.
But only if you
serve me well.
- Ow.
- Shh.
- It's not deep.
- I thought they were going to kill me.
They thought so, too.
He hated me,
the man who hit me.
I saw it in his eyes.
Hated me.
He never met me before,
but he wanted
to hurt me.
- Of course he did.
- Why? Why would a stranger--
you are everything
he will never have.
Your horse eats better
than his children.
It doesn't matter now.
He's dead.
I would have given them
bread if I had it.
I hate the King
more than any of them.
Don't say these things.
If the wrong
people hear you--
But you're not
the wrong people.
Don't trust anybody.
Life is safer
that way.
And where
are you going?
I have something for you
from Prince Theon.
- What?
- Me.
He says I'm to make
the rounds.
And keep you warm.
The Spice King refuses me
because I'm a bad investment.
The Silk King won't support me
because of his business with
the Lannisters.
Why offend
his best customer?
And the Copper King
offers me a single ship
on the condition that I lie
with him for a night.
Does he think I will
whore myself for a boat?
When I came to this city,
I had nothing.
Truly nothing.
I slept by the docks.
And when I could find work
loading the ships, I would eat.
If not,
I dreamed of food.
Today I am the richest
man in Qarth.
Do you think the path
from poverty to wealth
is always pure
and honorable?
I have done
many things, Khaleesi,
that a righteous man
would condemn.
And here I am,
with no regrets.
Bar the gates.
Ring the bells.
Slowly, Khaleesi.
Where are they?
Where are my dragons?!
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Download Movie Subtitles Searcher from www.OpenSubtitles.org